<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android">

    <string-array name="bcs_arr">
        <item>부족</item>
        <item>부족</item>
        <item>적정</item>
        <item>초과</item>
        <item>초과</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="uv_description_arr">
        <item>낮음</item>
        <item>보통</item>
        <item>높음</item>
        <item>매우높음</item>
        <item>위험</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ozone_description_arr">
        <item>좋음</item>
        <item>보통</item>
        <item>나쁨</item>
        <item>매우나쁨</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="wind_speed_description_arr">
        <item>약함</item>
        <item>약간강함</item>
        <item>강함</item>
        <item>매우강함</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="disease">
        <item>질병없음</item>
        <item>당뇨</item>
        <item>알러지</item>
        <item>치매</item>
        <item>관절염</item>
        <item>파보 장염</item>
        <item>비만</item>
        <item>암</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="language">
        <item>ko</item>
        <item>en</item>
        <item>ja</item>
        <item>ch</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="setting_title">
        <item>일반 설정</item>
        <item>사용자</item>
        <item>디바이스</item>
        <item>함께관리</item>
        <item>펫 관리</item>
        <item>고객관리</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="general_settings">
        <item>공지사항</item>
        <item>홈페이지</item>
        <item>앱 버전</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="user_settings">
        <item>계정</item>
        <item>알림</item>
        <item>측정단위</item>
        <!--<item>로그아웃</item>-->
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="device_settings">
        <item>배변판</item>
        <item>급식기</item>
        <item>침대</item>
        <item>방석</item>
        <item>하네스</item>
        <item>인식표</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="hodoo_link_settings">
        <item>그룹 멤버 리스트</item>
        <item>멤버 요청 기록</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pet_settings">
        <item>등록된 펫 리스트</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="support_settings">
        <item>오픈소스 라이선스</item>
        <item>이용약관</item>
        <item>개인정보처리방침</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="basic_info_activity__pet_breed">
        <item>마스티프</item>
        <item>보르도 마스티프</item>
        <item>로트바일러</item>
        <item>복서</item>
        <item>자이언트 슈나우저</item>
        <item>스탠더드 슈나우저</item>
        <item>도베르만 핀셔</item>
        <item>그레이트 데인</item>
        <item>불 마스티프</item>
        <item>저먼 셰퍼드</item>
        <item>코몬도르</item>
        <item>그레이트 피레니즈</item>
        <item>콜리</item>
        <item>캉갈</item>
        <item>올드 잉글리시 시프도그</item>
        <item>셔틀랜드 시프도그</item>
        <item>비어디드 콜리</item>
        <item>웰시 코기</item>
        <item>오스트레일리안 켈피</item>
        <item>벨지안 시프도그</item>
        <item>피레니안 마스티프</item>
        <item>보스롱</item>
        <item>티베탄 마스티프</item>
        <item>사모예드</item>
        <item>시베리안 허스키</item>
        <item>알래스칸 맬러뮤트</item>
        <item>아메리칸 에스키모 도그</item>
        <item>캐나디안 에스키모 도그</item>
        <item>아프간 하운드</item>
        <item>그레이하운드</item>
        <item>아이리시 울프하운드</item>
        <item>휘핏</item>
        <item>보르조이</item>
        <item>살루키</item>
        <item>아자와크</item>
        <item>닥스훈트</item>
        <item>미니어처 닥스훈트</item>
        <item>쿤 하운드</item>
        <item>오터 하운드</item>
        <item>노르위전 엘크하운드</item>
        <item>잉글리시 폭스하운드</item>
        <item>바셋하운드</item>
        <item>아메리칸 폭스하운드</item>
        <item>비글</item>
        <item>던커</item>
        <item>해리어</item>
        <item>슈바이처 라우프훈트</item>
        <item>스위스 하운드</item>
        <item>아르투아 하운드</item>
        <item>오가르 폴스키</item>
        <item>포르셀렌</item>
        <item>바센지</item>
        <item>로디지안 리지백</item>
        <item>치르네코 델레트나</item>
        <item>이비전 하운드</item>
        <item>파라오 하운드</item>
        <item>포덴코 카나리오</item>
        <item>저먼 와이어 헤어드 포인터</item>
        <item>바이마라너</item>
        <item>비즐라</item>
        <item>저먼 쇼트 헤어드 포인터</item>
        <item>잉글리시 포인터</item>
        <item>골든 리트리버</item>
        <item>래브라도 리트리버</item>
        <item>체서피크 베이 리트리버</item>
        <item>컬리 코티드 리트리버</item>
        <item>플랫 코티드 리트리버</item>
        <item>아이리시 세터</item>
        <item>고든 세터</item>
        <item>잉글리시 세터</item>
        <item>서섹스 스패니얼</item>
        <item>필드 스패니얼</item>
        <item>아이리시 워터 스패니얼</item>
        <item>클럼버 스패니얼</item>
        <item>아메리칸 코커 스패니얼</item>
        <item>아메리칸 워터 스패니얼</item>
        <item>웰시 스프링어 스패니얼</item>
        <item>잉글리시 스프링어 스패니얼</item>
        <item>잉글리시 코커 스패니얼</item>
        <item>폭스 테리어</item>
        <item>케리 블루 테리어</item>
        <item>맨체스터 테리어</item>
        <item>베들링턴 테리어</item>
        <item>스카이 테리어</item>
        <item>실리햄 테리어</item>
        <item>케언 테리어</item>
        <item>불 테리어</item>
        <item>웰시 테리어</item>
        <item>아이리시 테리어</item>
        <item>웨스트 하일랜드 화이트 테리어</item>
        <item>스태퍼드셔 불 테리어</item>
        <item>소프트 코티드 휘튼 테리어</item>
        <item>댄디 딘몬트 테리어</item>
        <item>미니어처 슈나우저</item>
        <item>스코티시 테리어</item>
        <item>오스트레일리안 테리어</item>
        <item>노리치 테리어</item>
        <item>에어데일 테리어</item>
        <item>잭 러셀 테리어</item>
        <item>핏불 테리어</item>
        <item>샤페이</item>
        <item>티베탄 테리어</item>
        <item>티베탄 스패니얼</item>
        <item>라사 압소</item>
        <item>프렌치 불도그</item>
        <item>보스턴 테리어</item>
        <item>스키퍼키</item>
        <item>키스혼드</item>
        <item>불도그</item>
        <item>비숑 프리제</item>
        <item>일본 스피츠</item>
        <item>차우차우</item>
        <item>달마티안</item>
        <item>스탠더드 푸들</item>
        <item>미니어처 푸들</item>
        <item>시바견</item>
        <item>아키타견</item>
        <item>삽살개</item>
        <item>제주개</item>
        <item>진돗개</item>
        <item>풍산개</item>
        <item>친</item>
        <item>말티즈</item>
        <item>일본 테리어</item>
        <item>잉글리시 토이 스패니얼</item>
        <item>파피용</item>
        <item>차이니스 크레스티드</item>
        <item>토이 맨체스터 테리어</item>
        <item>이탈리안 그레이하운드</item>
        <item>퍼그</item>
        <item>미니어처 핀셔</item>
        <item>페키니즈</item>
        <item>포메라니안</item>
        <item>아펜핀셔</item>
        <item>토이 푸들</item>
        <item>시추</item>
        <item>치와와</item>
        <item>요크셔 테리어</item>
        <item>실키 테리어</item>
        <item>브뤼셀 그리폰</item>
        <item>독일 스피츠</item>
        <item>미니어처 핀셔</item>
        <item>카발리에 킹 찰스 스패니얼</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="weight_tip_title">
        <item>Why Underweight Occurs in Dogs</item>
        <item>What to do if your Dog is Underweight </item>
        <item>Why You Should Watch Your Pet\'s Weight</item>
        <item>Health Risks in Overweight or Obese Dogs</item>
        <item>Health Risks in Overweight or Obese Dogs</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="weight_tip">
        <item>
            If your dog is underweight, there are several reasons why this may occur. Oftentimes when dogs are adopted from unkempt environments or unhealthy previous lifestyles they may already be underweight. If your dog is losing weight even though you feel you are doing everything correctly in terms of diet, there may still be some reasons why it is happening. Reasons include: Insufficient Diet If a dog is consuming a diet that is insufficient for their dietary needs, such as a medium or large breed dog being fed small breed dog food, then that could cause a dog to be underweight. In addition, if you are feeding your dog a home-cooked diet, or raw diet, you may be unknowingly missing out on some key nutrients your dog needs to gain weight. Underfeeding If your dog is underweight, you may not be feeding him enough at mealtime or enough times per day. Upon talking to your veterinarian, you will gain the knowledge of how much and how often to feed your companion. Parasites Parasites, namely worms, can invade a dog\'s gastrointestinal organs and prevent a dog from gaining weight. If your dog has intestinal worms, he may also be showing other symptoms, such as bloating. Diabetes Diabetes can cause a dog to be underweight. When a dog has an insulin shortage, he doesn\'t get any nourishment from the cells. Therefore, the energy comes from fat and muscle. Teeth Conditions If your dog has painful teeth, such as abscessed teeth or inflammation of the gums, he may not want to eat much due to the pain in his mouth. Also, if a dog has a painful jaw or jaw muscles, this could cause painful chewing. Disease There are many diseases that can cause a dog to be underweight. Cancer, pulmonary conditions, abdominal diseases, and other illnesses can cause a dog to have trouble keeping weight on. Medications If your dog is taking certain medications, side-effects from the medications can cause him to lose weight and have trouble gaining it back. Consult your veterinarian for a possible change of prescription.</item>
        <item>
           If you feel your dog is underweight, make an appointment with your veterinarian so this can be verified. Your veterinarian will perform a complete physical examination on your companion while asking you several questions about his diet. He will want to know how much food he eats and what type of food he enjoys. He will also ask questions pertaining to his lifestyle, such as how much he exercises and if he has an adequate amount of energy. He will also want to know if your dog is on any medications that may cause a side effect of lack of appetite. If he feels you are not feeding your dog enough, he may have you take a little time to see if he gains weight after increasing his caloric intake. If this does not work, you will need to go back to your veterinarian for a more detailed examination. Your veterinarian may choose to perform blood work, a biochemistry profile, urinalysis, and possibly an ultrasound of the abdomen to check for any abnormalities in his gastrointestinal tract. He may also perform an endoscopy to take a closer look at his esophagus and his stomach. These various tests, as well as other tests as determined by your medical professional, will find any type of disease or other medical condition which can lead to your dog not gaining enough weight.  Your veterinarian will also take a look at your dog\'s mouth, teeth and throat area. He will be looking for inflammation of the gums or any teeth abnormalities. Once the test results come in, your veterinarian may have an idea of what is causing your dog to remain underweight. Once your veterinarian comes to a diagnosis, he will explain treatment options for your companion. Once these treatment options begin to take hold, hopefully your companion will begin to gain weight.
        </item>
        <item>Studies indicate that nearly 50 percent of adult dogs and cats in the United States are overweight or obese, and that percentage increases among older pets. Obesity increases the risk for other serious health problems, including osteoarthritis, diabetes (in cats), heart and respiratory diseases, and many types of cancers. Extra weight also puts pets at increased risk for complications during anesthesia if they need to undergo surgery or other procedures. And if a pet already has a health condition, obesity makes the problem that much harder to manage. An overweight pet also deals with lower energy overall, hampering his ability to enjoy an active lifestyle with you and your family.</item>
        <item>
            1. Arthritis
Extra weight puts extra pressure on a dog\'s joints. The cartilage in the joint deteriorates, which leads to arthritis. Sure, we can give pain medications, but weight loss helps significantly.

2. ACL
Too much weight is a well-known risk factor for tearing the ACL (anterior cruciate ligament), an important ligament in the knee. A torn ACL must be repaired with surgery.

3. Heart and breathing conditions
Weight gain can cause heart disease and high blood pressure. It\'s also linked to breathing problems. Overweight dogs are more prone to a collapsing trachea and laryngeal paralysis.  Untreated, these airway conditions could lead to a respiratory crisis which could be fatal if not treated.

4. Anesthesia risk
The heart and lungs of overweight and obese dogs have to work harder during anesthesia. The dog struggles to breathe because he has difficulty expanding his chest. Dogs often sleep too deeply or not deeply enough. In addition, overweight dogs may take a long time to wake up after anesthesia.

5. Tumors
Obesity may increase the risk of certain tumors such as benign fatty tumors (lipomas), as well as breast and bladder cancer (transitional cell carcinoma).

6. Skin diseases
Overweight dogs have extra skin folds, which can cause irritation and infection by bacteria. This can lead to scratching, body odor and skin redness. Overweight dogs often have an unhealthy looking coat because it\'s harder, if not impossible, for them to groom effectively.

7. Quantity and quality of life
Obesity can take up to 2 years off the life of your dog! Quality of life is also lower. Carrying extra pounds around takes a toll; overweight dogs are slow to get down and up, they get winded or tired quickly and are less likely to play.
        </item>
        <item>
           1. Arthritis
Extra weight puts extra pressure on a dog\'s joints. The cartilage in the joint deteriorates, which leads to arthritis. Sure, we can give pain medications, but weight loss helps significantly.

2. ACL
Too much weight is a well-known risk factor for tearing the ACL (anterior cruciate ligament), an important ligament in the knee. A torn ACL must be repaired with surgery.

3. Heart and breathing conditions
Weight gain can cause heart disease and high blood pressure. It\'s also linked to breathing problems. Overweight dogs are more prone to a collapsing trachea and laryngeal paralysis.  Untreated, these airway conditions could lead to a respiratory crisis which could be fatal if not treated.

4. Anesthesia risk
The heart and lungs of overweight and obese dogs have to work harder during anesthesia. The dog struggles to breathe because he has difficulty expanding his chest. Dogs often sleep too deeply or not deeply enough. In addition, overweight dogs may take a long time to wake up after anesthesia.

5. Tumors
Obesity may increase the risk of certain tumors such as benign fatty tumors (lipomas), as well as breast and bladder cancer (transitional cell carcinoma).

6. Skin diseases
Overweight dogs have extra skin folds, which can cause irritation and infection by bacteria. This can lead to scratching, body odor and skin redness. Overweight dogs often have an unhealthy looking coat because it\'s harder, if not impossible, for them to groom effectively.

7. Quantity and quality of life
Obesity can take up to 2 years off the life of your dog! Quality of life is also lower. Carrying extra pounds around takes a toll; overweight dogs are slow to get down and up, they get winded or tired quickly and are less likely to play.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="meal_tip_title">
        <item>How to tame the right eating habits for pets!!</item>
        <item>What should I do with the children who eat unbalanced food?</item>
        <item>a recommended nutrient for pregnancy or breastfeeding, or companion animals.</item>
        <item>Dietary prescribing, will it really work?</item>
        <item>Dietary prescription, will it really work? Couldn\'t you give me less general feed?</item>
        <item>What should I do when I often walk?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="meal_tip">
        <item>You\'d better set the rules for paying your dog. Cats are animals that eat little by little a few times a day and dogs are animals that eat like humans. So cats are healthier when they eat for free, but dogs are healthier when they eat.

Dogs are less digestible than dogs until they are one year old, so it is better to eat more often when they are young. It is recommended to give four times a day to those under four months, and three times a day for five to eight months After eight months, you have to make a habit of serving two meals. It\'s best to calculate the amount of food you eat after you\'ve had a certain amount of time since you were a child. And if you give snacks often, you may end up in a bad habit of waiting for a better snack all the time without eating
</item>
        <item>If the dog that eats is not finished within a certain amount of time, please clean up the food. It gives you two chances per meal. If you don\'t eat on the second line, don\'t give me any other food or snacks until the next meal hour. The point is to inform your dog that the food you give him is precious, and to give him the sense that if you miss the opportunity, you will be hungry until you can eat next time. You have to have a strong heart when you are training. If you feel sorry, think, \'If you hurt your health with a bad food habit, you will feel even more sorry!\' Once you have a good food habit, you can grow healthy without having to fight food for the rest of your life.

It is recommended to set the time for snacks, such as setting the time for lunch. I only give it to you when I\'m praising you or after I\'ve finished eating. Also, snacks should not be given more than 10 percent of the amount of food you eat per day. Most snacks are made without regard to nutrition, just like snacks eaten by humans, and if you eat too much, you end up being undernourished or overworked, which can harm your health.
</item>
        <item>According to AAFCO, mother dogs and cats during pregnancy or breastfeeding have nutritional recommendations just like young animals. The dog\'s pregnancy period is approximately 63 days and the baby\'s weight increases a little until the 35th day of pregnancy (five weeks), so there\'s no special need to change the feed if the mother is eating well and maintaining a good weight. After five weeks of pregnancy, the growth of the fetus begins to accelerate, and the energy required increases, so you need to feed better and care about nutrients.

In general, just before the baby is born, the daily essential energy increases from 30% to 60% depending on the number of fetuses. However, even after the sixth week of pregnancy, the enlarged fetus may be pressured to eat less because of the need for nutrition. At this time, it is recommended to switch to dog food only for dogs under one year old to provide sufficient energy and nutrition. Dog food, which contains a lot of growth-essential nutrients such as calories and protein, can be nutritious enough even if you eat less, so you can expect healthier mothers and babies.

The breastfeeding period after delivery requires more energy than during pregnancy. Even at this time, keep feeding the dog to the mother. Also, during breastfeeding, you need a lot of water to make breast milk, so you should always prepare clean water to help you get enough water.
</item>
        <item>Most of the diet prescriptions sold on the market are designed to contain a lot of dietary fiber and are low in calories. Dietary fibers are carbohydrates, but they digest very little, so they have very little calories, which means they supply less calories than regular feed in the same volume. Also, fiber combines well with water and takes up a lot of volume, so it gives you a sense of satisfaction. In particular, soluble fiber can slow digestion, making pets less hungry.

Good diet foods contain not only enough essential nutrients, but also a lot of good diet ingredients. For example, supplementing essential amino acids can help prevent muscle loss during a diet. And with the addition of L-Carnitine, which promotes fat metabolism, it helps the body use more fat.

But most importantly, food is the total calorie content. You have to remember that no matter how good food you eat, you can\'t succeed if you eat too much.
</item>
        <item>There is no reason to choose a prescription. But prescription food is good for caregivers to diet their pets more comfortably. If you eat less regular food, your pet may feel hungry easily. Since most obese animals have a larger stomach size than normal animals, sudden reductions in their paychecks can often lead to behaviors such as walking.

A low-calorie diet can help. It is recommended that you reduce your salary slowly and achieve your target salary for one or two weeks. Because removing the stomach like a highly obese person is not yet performed on animals, we have to reduce the stomach capacity by slowly lowering the salary. For severe altitude obesity, you may have a longer time to reduce your salary, but it\'s a good idea to meet your target salary within a month.</item>
        <item>First of all, we need to tell if the act of cannibalism is caused by real hunger or food poisoning. You might want to ask for more pets just as people can eat more in front of delicious food. Never give food if you\'re a glutton for food. If you give food right away when you eat, you can make a bad habit. Moreover, if you give food to your companion without any knowledge of food, it can damage your health, so no matter how cute you ask, you should refuse it for the sake of your beloved.

If you\'re really hungry and eat something, you can give them snacks with less calories. You can give a little bit of feed or a little bit of low-calorie vegetables such as boiled cabbage, boiled broccoli and raw cucumbers. However, the next time you give food, remember to reduce the amount by taking into account the amount of snacks.
</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="notification_item">
        <item>모든 메시지 알림</item>
        <item>식사 알림</item>
        <item>무게 측정 알림</item>
        <item>그룹 초대 알림</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="risk_level_item">
        <item>낮음</item>
        <item>약간</item>
        <item>중간</item>
        <item>높음</item>
        <item>심각</item>
        <item>위험</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activity_question_title">
        <item>산책횟수</item>
        <item>활동성</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="walk_question">
        <item>주 1회</item>
        <item>주 2회</item>
        <item>주 3회</item>
        <item>주 4회</item>
        <item>주 5회</item>
        <item>주 6회</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activity_question">
        <item>조용한편</item>
        <item>보통인편</item>
        <item>활발한편</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="unit_str_arr">
        <item>cm / kg</item>
        <item>inch / lb</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="weight_unit">
        <item>kg</item>
        <item>lb</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="height_unit">
        <item>cm</item>
        <item>inch</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cat_type_physique_str_arr">
        <item>배 둘레</item>
        <item>다리길이</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="dog_type_physique_str_arr">
        <item>체장</item>
        <item>체고</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
